123kerala.com 2011-05-27

# Privacy Policy

123kerala.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: 123kerala.com. 

**Advertisers**

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and the cookies received with such ads are collected by those companies; we do not have access to this information. 

**Personal Information**

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. 

Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes. 

**External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. 123kerala.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Public Forums**

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [sanjeev@123kerala.com](mailto:sanjeev@123kerala.com)
